(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
USADA PEKORA 周年3D LIVE ぺこらRUSH！！！
USADA PEKORA Anniversary 3D LIVE: Pekora RUSH!!!
※この配信は演出により激しく点滅する場面がございます
部屋を明るくし画面から十分離れてご視聴ください
*This broadcast contains scenes with intense flashing lights due to the staging.
Please watch in a well-lit room and stay a sufficient distance from the screen.
君に 逢いたい時だって
Even when I want to see you
どこか 逢えない気持ちがある
There's a feeling that we somehow can't meet
だけど 本当の優しさが
But maybe a true kindness
そこに あるかも知れない
Might be right there
そこにあるかも知れない・・・ ~Special Full Version~
作詞・作曲：Daito Music
Maybe It's There... ~Special Full Version~
Lyrics & Composition: Daito Music
人込みに 揺られてる
Swayed by the crowd
どこかに 宛てがあるわけじゃない
It's not like I have a destination in mind
独りきり 歩いても
Even if I walk all alone
何か 解決することじゃない
It's not like it solves anything
自分が 本当に望んでる
The feelings that I
気持ちは きっと
Truly desire are surely...
これから 二人で
From now on, the two of us
歩いて行くことさ
Will walk together
君に 逢いたい時だって
Even when I want to see you
どこか 逢えない気持ちがある
There's a feeling that we somehow can't meet
だけど 本当の優しさが
But maybe a true kindness
そこに あるかも知れない
Might be right there
二人 輝いた季節は
The seasons we shone together
きっと これからも続いてく
Are surely going to continue from here on
だから 大切な未来に
So, into the precious future
この想いを 残したい
I want to leave these feelings behind
飽きるまで 話しても
Even if we talk until we're tired
全部 分かり合えるわけじゃない
It doesn't mean we'll understand everything
言葉より 伝えたい
Feelings I want to convey
気持ちが この胸にあふれてる
More than words are overflowing in my heart
君がいつか 探した夢の
The continuation of the dream
続きは きっと
You once searched for will surely...
二人で 描いて行こう
...be something the two of us draw together
忘れないで
Please don't forget
独りきり 孤独なようで
Though we seem all alone and lonely
皆 何かに悩んでいる
Everyone is troubled by something
すぐには 変わらないけれど
Although things won't change right away
とにかく 信じていたい
I want to believe no matter what
流した 涙捨て去って
Casting away the tears I've shed
ずっと 君のそばで生きたい
I want to live by your side forever
いつか 振り返った時に
Because I don't want to regret it
後悔 したくないから
When I look back someday
君に...
To you...
会いたいと言いたくて
I wanted to say I want to see you
二人...
The two of us...
輝いた季節は
In that season we shined
後悔したくないから
Because I don't want to have any regrets
叶わない 夢なんて
Dreams that don't come true
簡単に 口にはしたくない
Are things I don't want to speak of easily
諦めた 瞬間に
The very moment you give up
自分自身 終わらせてるだけ
You're just bringing an end to yourself
もっと 単純に感じたい
I want to feel things more simply
君のこと いつも
About you, I'll always
素直に 笑うよ
Smile with all my heart
未来は 続いてく
The future goes on and on
君が ホントにスキだって
That I really, truly love you
いつも 心に飾ってたい
Is what I want to keep in my heart forever
楽しさだけが 全てなら
If it was only about the fun
本当の 愛じゃないから
Then it wouldn't be real love
君に...
To you...
会いたいと言いたくて
I wanted to say I want to see you
二人 輝いた季節は
That season where we both shined
きっと これからも続いてく
Will surely continue from here on out
だから 大切な未来に
So, for our precious future
この想いを 残したい
I want to leave these feelings behind
君に...
To you...
会いたいと言いたくて
I wanted to say I want to see you
二人...
The two of us...
輝いた季節は
In that season we shined
みんな 6周年ライブに来てくれてアリぺこ！
Everyone, thank you-peko for coming to my 6th anniversary live!
そして大変お待たせしました！
And I'm so sorry to have kept you waiting!
すんません、すんません。
My apologies, my apologies.
けどね、みんなに楽しんでもらえるような
But you know, I've made this a live show
ライブになってるぺこだから是非ともお楽しみに！
that everyone can enjoy, so please look forward to it!
そして1曲目は「そこにあるかもしれない」を歌わせてもらったぺこ！
And for the first song, I sang 'Soko ni Aru Kamoshirenai'!
ま、っていうことは今回のテーマは... そう！パチスロ第2弾！イェーイ！
Well, which means this time's theme is... That's right! Pachislot Part 2! Yay!
当たり演出もね、めちゃめちゃ色々ありますんで、
There are tons of jackpot effects too,
是非とも次の曲は何来るかな？って考えながら
so I'd be happy if you enjoy guessing what song will come next
楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいぺこ！
while you watch!
そして今回のハッシュタグはこちら！
And here's the hashtag for this time!
「#兎田ぺこら6周年記念LIVE」ぺこなので、
It's '#UsadaPekora6thAnniversaryLIVE',
たくさんポストしてください！
so please post a lot!
ちゅうわけで、そんじゃ早速回していくか！
So with that, let's start spinning right away!
よいしょっと。あれ？
Heave-ho. Huh?
お、始まった！
Oh, it's started!
運命の一撃
A Strike of Destiny
笑うべきだとわかった時は泣くべきじゃねえぺこ！
When you know you should be laughing, you shouldn't be crying-peko!
運命の一撃を
The Strike of Destiny...
叩き込め！
Smash it in!
3（さん）！
3!
2（に）！
2!
1（いち）！
1!
咲かすか 枯らすか 今
To bloom or to wither, right now
燃えるように 陽が沈む
The sun sets as if it's burning
歯車が回る
The gears are turning
ラッパが鳴れば ジャッカサマサマ 真っ新の物語
When the trumpet sounds, Jack-a-sama-sama, a brand new story
はしゃがらばらば はしゃがらばらば 真っ赤な過去が追いかける
Frolicking and falling apart, a crimson past chases after me
道化師の笑み 仮面の裏側 どかしても消えない
The joker's smile behind the mask won't disappear even if moved
傷が痛んでも
Even if the wound hurts
咲かすか 枯らすか 現在
To bloom or to wither, the present
燃えるように 陽が沈む
The sun sets as if it's burning
真夜中の暗い孤独から 繰り出す
Moving out from the dark midnight solitude
微かに響く鐘が 陰る日々の道しるべ
A faintly echoing bell is the guidepost for the darkening days
音の鳴る先へ
Towards where the sound is made
ラッパが鳴れば ジャッカワラワラ 真っ新の演目の応酬
When the trumpet sounds, Jack-a-wara-wara, an exchange of brand new performances
真っ暗のまま 変わらぬ間 真逆様 突っ伏すのに
While it remains pitch dark and unchanging, even though falling face down head-first
足を掴まれ 奈落の底まで
Leg grabbed, down to the bottom of hell
明日をも忘れて 息もできない
Forgetting even tomorrow, unable to breathe
咲かすか 枯らすか 現在
To bloom or to wither, the present
眠るように 目を閉じる
Close eyes as if sleeping
身体中巡る猛毒から 逃げ出す
Escaping from the deadly poison flowing through my body
微かに響く鐘に 耳を澄ませ生きるのか
Will I live by listening closely to the faintly echoing bell?
どちらか選べ
Choose one or the other
さぁ
Come on
快楽を 爪のように 未来だけ 想えばいい
Pleasure, like a claw, just think about the future
過去を葬り去って
Bury the past away
咲かすか 枯らすか 現在
To bloom or to wither, the present
燃えるように 陽が沈む
The sun sets as if it's burning
真夜中の深い孤独から 繰り出す
Moving out from the deep midnight solitude
運命が壊れるような 声で叫べ 始まりの
Scream with a voice that could break fate, the signal
合図 幕は今 舞って踊るさ
For the start, the curtain now flutters and dances
最期には 涙流す だから今は 耐え進む
Shedding tears at the end, so for now, I endure and move forward
幕が降りる その時まで まだ 絶えず
Until the curtain falls, still, without ceasing
歯車が回る
The gears are turning
究極 Vモンキー！
Ultimate V Monkey!
ココロが止まらない
My heart won't stop
何かをするのに 理由なんかいらないね
I don't need a reason to do something
近づけるよ
I can bring it closer
君を見ているだけで
Just by looking at you
戦っているのよ
I am fighting
期待はどんな時でも
Expectations, at any time
もつれて迷い込む
Get tangled and lost
一か八か
All or nothing
夢に向かい加速する
Accelerating towards my dream
ココロが止まらない
My heart won't stop
感じてる
I'm feeling it
悩み多き日常のターンに
In the turns of a worry-filled daily life
君といる時の
The me when I'm with you
自分が一番好きだよ
Is the me I love most
ココロは止まらない
My heart won't stop
光の中
In the light
七色の水しぶきあげて
Raising a rainbow-colored spray of water
新しい明日の風に向かい走り出そうよ
Let's start running towards the wind of a new tomorrow
二人きりで
Just the two of us
会いたい気持ちが
The feeling of wanting to see you
ため息に溶けてゆく
Melts into a sigh
淋しいよ
I'm lonely
そばにいてくれた
You were by my side
泣き出しそうになった時
When I was about to burst into tears
気づかないふりしてくれたね
You pretended not to notice, didn't you?
重ねる唇から
From overlapping lips
こぼれる切なさも愛しさも
Overflowing sadness and love
ココロが止まらない
My heart won't stop
感じてる
I'm feeling it
もっとすべてを変えてみたい
I want to try changing everything more
願った奇跡がこんなにも近くにあったよ
The miracle I wished for was right here, so close
ココロは止まらない
My heart won't stop
通りすぎた夏の匂い懐かしいね
The scent of the passing summer is nostalgic
君を好きになってから前より淋しがり屋に
Since I fell in love with you, I've become lonelier than before
なってしまった
I have become
こわいものはたった一つ
There's only one thing I'm afraid of
君が優しすぎること
That's you being too kind
黄昏が風止めても
Even if the twilight stops the wind
夢へのブレーキがかからない
The brakes on my dream won't work
ココロが止まらない
My heart won't stop
感じてる
I'm feeling it
きっと答えは一つじゃない
Surely there's not just one answer
君に逢うためだけにとても優しくなれるよ
Just to meet you, I can become very kind
ココロは止まらない
My heart won't stop
月の雫
Moonlight droplets
ずっと君を探してた
I've been looking for you all this time
同じ時 同じ星 見上げてこのままきっと
Gazing at the same star at the same time, like this, surely
色褪せぬように
So that it doesn't fade
輝くマリンブルー
Shining marine blue
やっと出会えたサマータイム
Finally encountered summertime
ミラクルマリンパワー
Miracle marine power
せーので飛び込もう！
Let's jump in on the count of three!
Go! Go! Let's Go! SEA STORY
海物語 ~Go! Go! SEA STORY~ セカンドシーズン
Sea Story ~Go! Go! SEA STORY~ Second Season
太陽サンサン裸足で
The sun is shining, barefoot
駆け出していこうビーチへ
Let's run out to the beach
ココナッツ 冒険
Coconuts, adventure
見つけに行こう海のワンダーランド
Let's go find the ocean's wonderland
みんな歌えば
If everyone sings
イルカたちがジャンプ
The dolphins will jump
カニとタコのダンス
Crabs and octopuses dance
スペシャルな夢を描こう
Let's paint a special dream
輝くマリンブルー
Sparkling Marine Blue
やっと出会ったサマータイム
Summer time we finally met
ミラクル マリンパワー
Miracle Marine Power
「せーの」で飛び込もう
Let's dive in on "ready, go"
Go! Go! Let's Go!
SEA STORY
海底探検泳いで
Swimming on an undersea exploration
一緒に遊びに行こうよ
Let's go play together
笑顔が何よりの
A smile is better than anything
たったひとつの宝物だよ
It's our one and only treasure
シャチの背中に
On the back of an orca
サンゴのトンネル
Through a coral tunnel
クジラのリズム
The rhythm of a whale
始まる夢のステージ
The stage of dreams begins
きらめくマリンスノー
Shimmering marine snow
みんな一緒に Everyday
Everyone together every day
スペシャル サマータイム
Special summer time
「せーの」で始めよう
Let's start on "ready, go"
Go! Go! Let's Go!
SEA STORY
輝くマリンブルー
Sparkling Marine Blue
やっと出会ったサマータイム
Summer time we finally met
ミラクル マリンパワー
Miracle Marine Power
「せーの」で飛び込もう
Let's dive in on "ready, go"
グレート マリンブルー
Great Marine Blue
水平線の彼方まで
Beyond the horizon
ミラクル マリンパワー
Miracle Marine Power
「せーの」で飛び込もう
Let's dive in on "ready, go"
Go! Go! Let's Go!
SEA STORY
ルパン三世のテーマ
Theme of Lupin III
BIG CHANCE
真赤な薔薇は あいつの唇
The crimson rose is her lips
やさしく抱きしめて くれとねだる
She begs for a gentle embrace
瞳の奥に 獲物を映して
Reflecting the prey deep in her eyes
寂しく問いかける 愛の在りか
Loneliness asks where love is
男には 自分の世界がある たとえるなら
A man has his own world, if one were to compare it...
空をかける ひとすじの流れ星
To a single shooting star streaking across the sky
孤独な笑みを 夕陽にさらして
Exposing a lonely smile to the setting sun
背中で泣いている 男の美学
Crying with his back turned, that is a man's aesthetics
背中で泣いてる　男の美学
The aesthetic of a man, crying behind his back
真珠の色は　あいつのまなざし
The color of pearls is in those eyes of hers
遥かな幸せを　夢に描く
Picturing distant happiness in a dream
いためることを　恐れるあまりに
Too afraid of causing any pain
冷たく突き放す　愛もあるさ
There's even a love that coldly pushes away
男には　自分の世界がある　たとえるなら
A man has his own world, if I were to compare it...
風をはらい　荒れくるう稲光
To a flash of lightning through the driving wind
都会の闇に　体を溶かして
Melting into the darkness of the city
口笛吹いてる　男の美学
The aesthetic of a man, whistling away
Amazing Grace
How sweet the sound
That saved a wretch
Like me
乙女アタック　突入！
Otome Attack, BEGIN!
いざ勝負！
Let's do this!
いくぞぺこ！
Here I go, peko!
いざ勝負！
Let's do this!
楽勝ぺこー！
Easy win, peko!
夜を彷徨う影が　光を遮ろうと吠える
The shadows wandering the night howl to block the light
罪深き羊たち　来なさい　容赦はしません
O sinful sheep, come forth; I shall show no mercy
守るべき人のため　優しい心のために
For those to be protected, for a kind heart
共に祈りましょう　御意に　誓う今かけて　挑戦を
Let us pray together; By your will, I swear now...
信じた仲間達と　この手に宿る力信じて
With the comrades I believed in, believing in the power within these hands
この手に宿る力信じて
Believing in the power within these hands
狂い咲けよ 闘志の華よ
Bloom wildly, flower of fighting spirit
戦の地に降り立つ夢
A dream that descends upon the land of battle
大輪の炎 闇をかき散らして
Scatter the darkness with the flames of large blossoms
勇気と熱を盾に 掴め
With courage and passion as your shield, seize it
辿り着こう 金色の空
Let's reach the golden sky
笑顔を育む大地へ
To the land that nurtures smiles
夜はいずれ去り 朝が訪れる
The night will eventually fade, and the morning will come
全てを越えて 君の愛叶う
Beyond everything, your love will come true
星の巡りを辿り 手にした希望の十字
Tracing the cycle of the stars, the cross of hope I held
後悔などしないわ
I won't have any regrets
赦しは私が与える
I am the one who gives forgiveness
発条仕掛けの意 濡れ影よ 光が導きし舞
Clockwork intent, a wet shadow, a dance guided by light
遊びはおしまい
Playtime is over
大胆不敵な場所 魂震え咲く艶
A fearless place, a luster where the soul trembles and blooms
勝利の扉開く鍵
The key to opening the door of victory
今生まれる楽園
A paradise born now
さぁ 共に行きましょう
Come, let's go together
正義は必ず勝つ いつまでも
Justice always wins, forever
空を渡る 溢れだし燃える想いが 鮮やかに彩る虹へ
Crossing the sky, overflowing burning feelings turn into a vividly colored rainbow
伸ばす手と手 瞳を交わして絆を結べば
If we stretch out our hands and exchange glances to form a bond
見えてくる新しい朝が
A new morning will come into view
時を越えて
Beyond time
暁の幸せはほら 誰の上にも降り注ぐ
Look, the happiness of dawn falls upon everyone
胸の中を 雨はやがて止み渇きを癒すよ
Within the heart, the rain will eventually stop and quench the thirst
過去を解き放て 君の夢を問う
Release the past, ask your dream
貴方と想いを 数えきれないほどの出会いと別れ重ねて
With you and my feelings, layering countless encounters and partings
真実 人は生きる意味を見つける
In truth, people find the meaning of life
狂い咲けよ 闘志の華よ
Bloom wildly, flower of fighting spirit
戦の地に降り立つ夢
A dream that descends upon the land of battle
大輪の炎 闇をかき散らして
Scatter the darkness with the flames of large blossoms
勇気と熱を盾に 掴め
With courage and passion as your shield, seize it
辿り着こう 金色の空
Let's reach the golden sky
笑顔を育む大地へ
To the land that nurtures smiles
祝福が
Blessings...
夜はいずれ去り 朝が訪れる
...the night will eventually fade, and the morning will come
全てを越えて 君の愛叶う
Beyond everything, your love will come true
待っていたぞ、ぺこら
I've been waiting for you, Pekora
バトルボーナス、ゲットー！
Battle Bonus, get!
Welcome to this crazy Time
このイカれた時代へようこそ君は
Welcome to this crazy era, you are...
tough boy tough boy tough boy tough boy
まともな奴ほど feel so bad
The more sane someone is, the more they feel so bad
正気でいられるなんて運がイイぜ you
It's lucky that you can stay sane, you
tough boy tough boy tough boy tough boy
時はまさに世紀末
Time is truly at the end of the century
淀んだ街角で僕らは出会った
We met on a stagnant street corner
Keep you burning 駆け抜けて
Keep you burning, run through
この腐敗と自由と暴力のまっただなか
In the midst of this corruption, freedom, and violence
No boy no cry 悲しみは
No boy no cry, sadness is...
絶望じゃなくて明日のマニフェスト
...not despair, but the manifesto for tomorrow
We are living,
living in the eighties
We still fight,
fighting in the eighties
どこもかしこも傷だらけ
Everywhere is covered in wounds
うずくまって泣いてても始まらないから
Crouching down and crying won't start anything
tough boy tough boy tough boy tough boy
どっちを向いても feel so sad
No matter where I look, I feel so sad
だけど死には至らない 気分はどうだい？
But it won't kill me, how are you feeling?
tough boy tough boy tough boy tough boy
ここは永遠のロックランド
This is the eternal Rockland
拳を握りしめ 僕らは出会った
We met with our fists clenched
Keep you burning 駆け抜けて
Keep you burning, run through it all
この狂気と希望と幻滅のまっただなか
In the midst of this madness, hope, and disillusionment
No boy no cry 進まなきゃ
No boy no cry, I have to move forward
勢いを増した向かい風の中を
Through the strengthening headwind
We are living, living in the eighties
We still fight, fighting in the eighties
野うさぎ討伐戦、突入！
Wild Rabbit Extermination Battle, start!
お前の英雄は、超うさぎが勝ってるぺこ！
Your hero... Super Rabbit is winning, peko!
PUSHぺこ！
PUSH, peko!
ごちそうさまでした！
Thank you for the meal!
This is a fate that brought us here watch my Long shot
Long shot
Feel like I am falling into the flame of lies
Tell me what you want from me
Try not to step back to where I used to belong
Looking for the escape from pain
I will cross my fingers hoping not to be sacrificed
目をそらさないで いつもの希望を胸に
Don't look away, with hope always in your heart
Get in the way, get ready for the time to come
浮かび上がりしシルエット追いかけ
Chasing the rising silhouette
Don't judge the reason why I'm standing here alone
Maybe it's already too late to regain
埋め尽くして影の火を 隠さないで
Fill it all up, don't hide the fire of the shadows
If I could write my wrongs and save you from the pain
It's not enough, it's not enough for me to break
The rule upon this world
I will never gonna leave you never wanna lose you we'll make it in the end
Not backing down for real
I won't trace someone else's life
I know who I am
Blame me if I messed up anything
Take the risk of everything
Justify this cruel world
甘い罠にして
Falling into a sweet trap
叫び声 震え
Screams trembling
飲み込まれていく
Being swallowed up
影を残して
Leaving a shadow behind
I will cross my fingers
Hoping not to be sacrificed
Use selfishness that keeps us moving forward
Get involved, get ready
For the time to come
浮かび上がる シルエット
A silhouette emerges
追いかけ
Chasing after it
Don't be afraid to be yourself
It's our yeah
何度だっていいんだ
It doesn't matter how many times
覚悟してんだ
I'm prepared
全て
Everything
守ると決めたよ
I've decided to protect it
君がいるから
Because you are here
絡み合う 未来を
The intertwined future
この手で
With these hands
変えてみせると して
I will change it
すべきことは
What needs to be done
分かっているから
Because I already know
Take this pain away from me
この胸の
Along with this
鼓動に 乗せて
Heartbeat in my chest
There's no way I can fail
研ぎ澄ませて
Sharpening it
星を
The stars
願った
I wished upon
強欲だ
Greedy
超強欲 BONUS
SUPER GREEDY BONUS
Found down the reason why
I'm standing here all alone
Maybe it's already too late
To regain
運命として掲げた日を
The day held up as destiny
なくさないで
Don't ever lose it
Brace yourself
Don't forget this is your fate
What if I could rewrite my wrongs
And save you from the pain?
It's not enough
It's not enough for me
To break
The rule of this world
I will never gonna leave you
Never wanna lose you
I'll make it in the end
Not backing down for real
I won't change
Someone else's life
I know who I am
待っていたのはこの瞬間
This is the moment I've been waiting for
待っていたのはこの瞬間！
This is the moment I've been waiting for!
ボーナス確定ぺこ！
Bonus confirmed, peko!
BONUS 確定
BONUS CONFIRMED
錬金術師に 在り得ぬもの...
That which is impossible for an alchemist...
黄金御成
Golden Attainment
一撃で じりじりと...
With a single strike, bit by bit...
みんなの 魂...
Everyone's soul...
聞こえますか？
Can you hear it?
彼方 広がる 無限
The infinity spreading beyond
手に 解き放て
Unleash it with your hands
聞こえますか？
Can you hear it?
命 始まる 脈動
The pulse of life beginning
愛を 突き上げて
Thrusting up your love
遥か 彼方
Far away in the distance
確かな 音楽と なった
It became a certain music
あの日
On that day
風は 泣いて
The wind cried
笑い やがて
Laughed, and eventually
伝え 紡ぐ
Communicated and spun
鼓動を
The heartbeat
歌に した
Into a song
そして
And then
夢は 開くよ
Dreams will open up
見たことない 世界の 果て
At the edge of a world never seen before
Yes, just believe
神様も 知らない
Even God doesn't know
ヒカリで
With light
歴史を 創ろう
Let's create history
不死なる ほど
Immortal enough
未来 照らす
To illuminate the future
一緒に飛ばないか？
Won't you fly with me?
Just believe 涙で濡れた羽根
Just believe, wings soaked with tears
重くて羽撃けない日は
On days they're too heavy to flap
その右手に添えよう
I'll place it in that right hand
描くチカラを
The power to create
鳥のように羽撃き合うよ
Flapping our wings like birds
Singing heart
いつの日か分かるときが来るから
Because the day will come when you'll understand
ずっと忘れない
I'll never forget
そのときには心のあるがままに
In that moment, just as your heart dictates
笑顔忘れない
I won't forget my smile
言葉なんていらない
I don't need any words
まだ見ぬ地平の先
Beyond the unseen horizon
強く信じて繋ぎ合う
Believing strongly and connecting with each other
ハーモニー舞う七色の翼
Harmony dancing with seven-colored wings
そして生きる今を
And the present we live in
見たことない明日の先へ
Toward a tomorrow we've never seen
Yes, just believe 千年後の今日も
Yes, just believe, even a thousand years from today
生まれ変わって歌いたい
I want to be reborn and sing
暖かいよ
It's warm
この温もり
This warmth
絶対離さない
I'll never let go
Just believe 運命なんてない
Just believe, there's no such thing as fate
物語は自分にある
The story lies within yourself
逃げ出したくなったら
If you feel like running away
宇宙を見上げよう
Let's look up at the universe
勇気こそが輝くんだよ
Courage is what truly shines
Singing star
遥か
Far away
星が音楽となったかの日
The day the stars became music
多分共に出会い響き
Perhaps we met and resonated together
神話のひとつのように
Like a single piece of mythology
紡いだ何も怖くないよ
We spun it together, so I'm not afraid of anything
見たことない世界の果て
To the ends of a world we've never seen
Yes, just believe...
神様も知らない
Even God doesn't know
ヒカリで歴史を創ろう
Let's create history with light
不死なる太陽
The immortal sun
未来照らす 一緒に飛ばないか？
Illuminating the future, won't you fly with me?
Just believe 涙で濡れた羽根
Just believe, wings soaked with tears
重くて羽撃けない日は
On days they're too heavy to flap
旋律は溶け合い
The melodies melt together
シンフォニーへと
Into a symphony
鳥のように羽撃き合うよ
Flapping our wings like birds
Singing heart
虹は架かる
A rainbow spans across
すべては夢と共に
Everything is together with our dreams
野うさぎ剣を押し込め！
Push in the Nousagi Sword!
行け 疾風のごとく
Go, like a gale
宿命の剣士よ
O fated swordsman
闇に紛れて
Mixing into the darkness
なにゆえ戦う
For what reason do you fight?
それは剣に聞け
Ask the sword.
正義だとか愛など
Justice, love, and the like
俺は追いかけない
I do not chase them.
闇に生まれ 闇に忍び
Born in darkness, hiding in darkness
闇を切り裂く
Tearing through the darkness
遙かな
From ancient times
いにしえから受け継いだ
I've inherited
使命だから
This mission.
行け！ 疾風のごとく
Go! Like a gale
魔戒の剣士よ
Makai Knight!
月満つる夜に
On the night of the full moon
金色になれ
Become golden.
雄々しき姿の
With a valiant form
孤独な戦士よ
Oh, lonely warrior!
魂を込めた
With your soul infused
怒りの刃 叩きつけて
Strike with your blade of rage.
時代に輝け
Shine through the ages.
牙狼！
Garo!
いつかおまえには
I want you to understand
分かって欲しい
someday.
戦いだけに生きた
Of me, who lived only
俺の胸のうちを
for battle.
愛にはぐれ 愛を憎み
Wandering from love, hating love
愛を求める
Seeking love
わずかな
A fleeting
安らぎさえ打ち捨てた
peace, I've cast aside.
誓いだけど
That is my vow.
立て！ 修羅のごとく
Arise! Like a Shura
魔戒の剣士よ
Makai Knight!
運命の歌の
As the song of destiny
命ずるままに
commands.
月夜に輝く
Shining in the moonlit night
孤高の戦士よ
Oh, solitary warrior!
迫り来る影を
The approaching shadows
一網打尽 叩き斬って
sweep them all away.
気高く吠えろ
Howl with nobility.
牙狼！
Garo!
行け！ 疾風のごとく
Go! Like a gale
魔戒の剣士よ
Makai Knight!
月満つる夜に
On the night of the full moon
金色になれ
Become golden.
雄々しき姿の
With a valiant form
孤独な戦士よ
Oh, lonely warrior!
魂を込めた
With your soul infused
怒りの刃 叩きつけて
Strike with your blade of rage.
時代に輝け
Shine through the ages.
牙狼！
Garo!
行け！ 疾風のごとく
Go! Like a gale
定めの剣士よ
Knight of destiny!
闇に光を
Bring light to the darkness.
警告
Warning
ボーナス、確定
Bonus confirmed
今度こそ君だけは幸せにしてみせるぺこ
This time, I'll definitely make only you happy, peko.
ボーナス確定
Bonus confirmed
これが実力ぺこ
This is my true power, peko.
悲しい日々が化石に変わるよ
Sad days will turn into fossils
もうすぐ
very soon
あなたのその痛みを眠りの森へと
Into the forest of sleep, I'll take your pain
密やかに導いてあげる
and lead you there quietly.
おやすみすべてに
Goodnight to everything,
一途すぎた迷い子たち
to the stray children who were too earnest.
はかない たゆたい 夢に
In a fleeting, drifting dream,
シンクロする日まで
until the day we synchronize.
命はまぶしい 朝を待っている
Life is waiting for the radiant morning
最後の懺悔もかなわないなら
if even the last confession cannot be granted.
いつか時代の夜が明ける
Someday the night of this era will break.
世界よ まぶたを閉じて
Oh world, close your eyelids.
命は目覚めて 時を紡ぎ出す
Life wakes up and begins to spin time
あなたの証拠をさかのぼるように
as if to trace back the evidence of your existence.
そして光が胸に届く
And then the light will reach your heart.
心よ原始に戻れ
O heart, return to the origin!
涙の岸辺で ずっとたたずんだ
Standing forever on the shore of tears,
気持ちを
these feelings...
優しく包むように 秘密の薬が
Like a gentle embrace, a secret medicine
思い出の沖へと運ぶよ
will carry them to the offshore of memories.
おやすみ モラルに
Goodnight to morals,
汚れていた指も耳も
to the fingers and ears that were soiled.
この腕の中で さあ 眠りなさい
Within these arms, now, please sleep.
命はまぶしい 朝を待っている
Life is waiting for the radiant morning
破れた聖書を抱きしめるより
instead of clutching a torn Bible.
いつか時代の夜が明ける
Someday the night of this era will break.
あなたよ 祈りを捨てて
You, throw away your prayers.
命は目覚めて 時を紡ぎ出す
Life wakes up and begins to spin time
自然の法則に その身をまかせ
entrusting your body to the laws of nature.
そして光が胸に届く
And then the light will reach your heart.
心よ原始に戻れ
O heart, return to the origin!
命はまぶしい 朝を待っている
Life is waiting for the radiant morning
最後の懺悔もかなわないなら
if even the last confession cannot be granted.
いつか時代の夜が明ける
Someday the night of this era will break.
世界よ まぶたを閉じて
Oh world, close your eyelids.
命は目覚めて 時を紡ぎ出す
Life wakes up and begins to spin time
あなたの証拠をさかのぼるように
as if to trace back the evidence of your existence.
そして光が胸に届く
And then the light will reach your heart.
心よ原始に戻れ
O heart, return to the origin!
ノエル…
Noel...
フレア…
Flare...
マリン…
Marine...
みんなどこ行っちゃったぺこなの…
Everyone, where did you all go, peko?
まぁいっか、3期生ならなんとかなるよな、きっと。
Oh well, I'm sure the 3rd gen will be fine.
ということで、ここまでたくさんのゲストのみんなとたくさんの曲を歌ってきましたが、
So, I've sung many songs with many guests so far,
みんな、様子はどうぺこ？
but how are you all doing, peko?
外のところは当たってましたか？
Did you win in other places?
楽しんでくれてますか？
Are you enjoying it?
最後にもね、一曲ぺこらまた歌いますので
I'll be singing one more song at the end,
そちらもお楽しみにということで
so please look forward to that too.
ここからは、グッズ紹介！
From here on, it's the goods introduction!
お、ぺかった！
Oh, it lit up!
お？ということは？
Oh? Which means?
キタキター！設定6ー！
It came! Setting 6!
ということで
So,
兎田ぺこら活動6周年記念グッズを紹介するぺこ！
I'm going to introduce the Usada Pekora 6th Anniversary goods!
まずは一つ目はこちらから。トゥルン！
First, here's the first one. Ta-da!
ぺこら推し法被！
Pekora Oshi Happi Coat!
こちらは悠久はぐれ先生に描いていただきました。
This was illustrated by Yuki Hagure-sensei.
もうね、着るだけで推しをアピールできる。イベントでも着てきてほしいぺこです。
You can show off your oshi just by wearing it. I'd love for you to wear it to events.
めちゃめちゃ可愛い法被ぺこなので、是非ともよろしくぺこ！
It's a super cute happi coat, so please check it out!
そして二つ目はこちら！トゥルン！
And the second one is this! Ta-da!
な、なんと、ついに！ぺこらマミーも写っているグッズが出てしまいました！
W-Wow, finally! A good featuring Pekora Mommy has been released!
こちらラバーマットです！
This is a rubber mat!
イラストはひこさんにお願いしております。
The illustration is by Hikosan.
テーマはカジノの兎田ぺこらと、
The theme is Usada Pekora in a casino,
ぺこらマミーです！
and Pekora Mommy!
ついにでてしまった、マミーが！だからね、ぺこらマミー大好きな人もお手にとってもらえると嬉しいぺこです。
Mommy finally made it! So, I'd be happy if Pekora Mommy fans could get their hands on it too.
そしてラバーマットがあるということは、三つ目はこちら！
And, since there's a rubber mat, the third one is this!
はい！カードスリーブもちゃんとあるぺこです！60枚入りでね。
Yes! There are card sleeves too! It's a pack of 60.
イラストは先ほどと同じくひこさんにお願いしております。
The illustration is also by Hikosan.
なんとこちら、ホロカでも使えますので、是非ともホロカで遊んでいる方は使っていただけると嬉しいぺこです。
And guess what, you can use them for HoloKa! So if you play HoloKa, I'd be happy if you used them.
そして四つ目はこちら！
And the fourth one is this!
可愛いね！ぺこらぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
It's so cute! The Pekora plushie keyholder!
カバンにつけてもよし、旅行先に持っていくのもよしの、持ち運びやすいサイズのぬいぐるみとなっているぺこ！
Good for your bag, or for taking on trips, it's a plushie that's just the right size to carry around!
こちら、なんとフルセット購入の特典がございます！
And there's actually a bonus for buying the full set!
数量限定で直筆サイン入りポストカードがあります！
In limited quantities, there's a hand-signed postcard!
通常バージョンは箔押し複製サイン入りのポストカードとなっておりまして、はぐれ先生のハッピのイラストとなっております。
The regular version comes with a foil-stamped printed signature postcard, featuring Hagure-sensei's happi illustration.
是非とも、じゃんじゃんバリバリ買ってぺこ！
Please buy lots and lots of them!
それでは最後は何の曲かな？
Now, what will the final song be?
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
お？あれ？
Oh? Huh?
エラー？
Error?
係員をお呼びください。
Please call a staff member.
ちょっと！店員！ライブできないライブできない！
Wait! Staff! I can't do the live, I can't do the live!
直してちょうだい！
Please fix it!
おい監視カメラ見えてんだろ！おいどこだどこだ！
Hey, you can see me on the monitor, right? Hey, where are you?
係員をお呼びください。
Please call a staff member.
お、いたいたいたいたいた！
Oh, there you are!
直して早く！ライブできないぺこだよ！
Fix it, hurry! I can't do the live!
係員をお呼びください。
Please call a staff member.
叩いててもダメぺこでしょ！
You shouldn't be hitting it!
叩いて蹴っても直らないだろ！
Hitting and kicking it won't fix it!
ちょっと！しっかりして！
Wait! Get a hold of yourself!
お、直った！
Oh, it's fixed!
あれ？
Huh?
仮想の世に生まれ 生きること
To be born and live in a virtual world,
すなわち 戦い、勝つこと
that is to say, to fight and to win.
時代と戦い 己が宿命と戦い 己自身に打ち勝つ
Fight the era, fight your destiny, and overcome yourself.
いつの世も大差はなし
It's the same in any era.
人の生き様が 一瞬の煌めきが
The way people live, a momentary sparkle,
歴史をつむいでいく
spins the thread of history.
今こそ胸に刻め 我が生き様を！
Now, carve my way of life into your heart!
永久に語り継げ 兎田の魂を
Tell the story of the Usada soul forever.
戦の炎、灯してみせよう！
I'll show you how I light the flames of battle!
(Are you ready?)
Shall We Dance? 始めよう
Shall We Dance? Let's begin
勝利の祝杯あげる前に
Before raising the victory toast
Relax Your Body 深呼吸
Relax Your Body, take a deep breath
そうすりゃだんだん高まる
Then it will gradually rise
Passion, Force
Passion Force
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A
腰をもっと引き上げたら右手を上げYEAH!
Lift your hips more, then raise your right hand, YEAH!
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A
〇〇〇〇〇〇六文銭
Circle circle circle circle circle circle Rokumonsen (Six Coins)
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A
まだまだ行けるはずだもっともっともっともっと!
You can still keep going, more, more, more, more!
Take A Chance! Take A Chance!
勝利のために
For the sake of victory
Take A Chance! Take A Chance!
Well Done!
SANADA DA DA SANADA DA DA
日ノ本一の兵(つわもの)
The greatest warrior in Japan
CHA RA CHA CHA CHA CHA RA CHA CHA CHA
不惜身命だぜ
Devoting my life without hesitation
SANADA DA DA SANADA DA DA
急げ夜が明ける前に
Hurry, before the night ends
CHA RA CHA CHA CHA RA CHA CHANCE
熱く熱く構えたなら
If you take a hot, hot stance
踊れ!歌え!SANADANCE 踊(NI)CISE さぁ
Dance! Sing! SANADANCE ODONICISE, come on!
Wow Wow Wow...
(It's Cypher time)
Close your eyes 瞑想
Close your eyes, meditation
Don't think... Feel
感覚研ぎ澄ませたなら高まる
Once your senses are sharpened, it heightens
Passion Force
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A
フロントキックでツイストかまして視線は下げずにハイ、ポーズ!
Do a front kick with a twist, keep your eyes up, and strike a pose!
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A
回って回ってブンブン回って回転スピード増し増し
Spinning, spinning, spinning around, increasing rotation speed!
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A
勢い付けてそうだ!もっともっともっともっと!
Building momentum, that's it! More, more, more, more!
Change the world! Change the world!
Do or Do not
There is no try
SANADA DA DANCE SANADA DA DANCE
ハート燃やして不夜城
Burning your heart in the nightless castle
CHA RA CHA CHA CHA CHA RA CHA CHA CHA
但惜身命だぜ
Cherishing my life
SANADA DA DANCE SANADA DA DANCE
心躍らせるために
To make your heart dance
CHA RA CHA CHA CHA RA CHA CHANCE
熱く熱く構えたなら
If you take a hot, hot stance
走れ!回せ!朱の棒だ!
Run! Spin! It's the red staff!
運命(さだめ)伸ばせ 空に叫べ SANADANCE 踊(NI)CISE さぁ
Extend your destiny, scream to the sky, SANADANCE ODONICISE, come on!
Wow Wow Wow...
苦しい時や辛い時には体を動かせよ SANADANCE
When times are hard or painful, move your body, SANADANCE
天上天下 唯我独尊 みんなで踊ろうぜ SANADANCE Let's Go!
Above heaven, under heaven, I alone am worthy of honor, let's all dance, SANADANCE, Let's Go!
Take A Chance! Change the world!
深呼吸
Deep breath
Ba Hoo!
本日も最終最後のお時間まで、兎田ぺこら6周年ライブにお付き合いいただきまして、誠にありがとうございました。
Thank you very much for staying with us until the very end of Usada Pekora's 6th Anniversary Live today.
はい、ありがとうございました。ありがとうございました。
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you very much.
残念ではございますが、まもなく本日のライブはすべて終了とさせていただきます。
Regrettably, today's live will soon come to a complete close.
メンバーシップカードをお持ちのお客様にご案内申し上げます。
Here is an announcement for customers who hold a membership card.
メンバーシップカードをお持ちの方は、このあとの10時15分より行われる、アンコールライブにもご参加いただけます。
For those who have a membership card, you can also participate in the encore live starting at 10:15 PM later tonight.
お持ちでない方もまだ間に合いますので、これを機にぜひ、ご加入ください。
Even if you don't have one, it's not too late, so please take this opportunity to join.
また、グッズ販売の方もまもなくカートオープンとなります。
Additionally, the merchandise sales cart will be opening soon.
10時10分より販売となりますので、ご購入をご検討のみなさまは、販売サイトにてご購入ください。
Sales will begin at 10:10 PM, so for those considering a purchase, please do so at the sales site.
明日のご案内を申し上げます。
Here is the announcement for tomorrow.
明日の営業は通常通り夜から配信を行います。
Tomorrow's business will proceed as usual with a stream in the evening.
明日も兎田ぺこら張り切ってまいりますので、ご来店お待ちしております。
Usada Pekora will be in high spirits tomorrow as well, so we look forward to your visit.
大変名残惜しくはございますが、本日はこれにてライブ終了とさせていただきます。
It's very hard to say goodbye, but with this, we conclude today's live performance.
最終最後までお付き合いいただき、ありがとうございました。
Thank you for staying with us until the very end.